[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Henry Pu Yi?", "correct_answer": "The last Emperor of China.", "incorrect_answers": ["The last of Maos supporters to be killed.", "First Asian to win a Nobel Prize.", "The first man to win a Pulitzer Prize and a Nobel Prize."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the popular Indonesian dish Mie goreng mean?", "correct_answer": "Fried noodles", "incorrect_answers": ["Crawling snakes", "Hair tuft", "Green mixture"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word means the study of drug action?", "correct_answer": "pharmacology", "incorrect_answers": ["enology", "chirology", "physiognosy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does the movie Grease 2 tie in with the movie Grease?", "correct_answer": "Michael is Sandy Olssons cousin.", "incorrect_answers": ["Rizzo from Grease is Paulettes mother.", "Johnny is Kenickies little brother.", "The only similarities are Crater-Face, Principal Mcgee and Blanche."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which British movie won 8 Oscars?", "correct_answer": "Gandhi", "incorrect_answers": ["Mrs. Miniver", "A Room With A View", "Oliver!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What professional team did hockey great Wayne Gretzky start his career with?", "correct_answer": "Edmonton Oilers", "incorrect_answers": ["Los Angeles Kings", "St Louis Blues", "New York Rangers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the epic movie Braveheart, William Wallace won his first major victory at what battle?", "correct_answer": "The Battle of Stirling Bridge", "incorrect_answers": ["The Battle of Yorkshire", "The Battle of Falkirk", "The Battle of Bannockburn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most of the pages on the Web are written in HTML.  It stands for this.", "correct_answer": "Hyper Text Markup Language", "incorrect_answers": ["Hillarious Text Message Language", "Hardened Text Message Language", "Hyper Text Make-up Language"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rokko island, constructed between 1973 and 1992, is an artificial island situated in which country?", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "China", "The Netherlands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of these is not a true breed of cat. Which one?", "correct_answer": "French Twist", "incorrect_answers": ["Pixie-bob", "Maine coon", "Ragdoll"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Komodo dragon, the largest living lizard on Earth, lives in which part of the world?", "correct_answer": "Indonesia", "incorrect_answers": ["North America", "South-western China", "Madagascar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what 1993 sci-fi movie does Jeff Goldblum portray mathematician and chaos theorist, Dr. Ian Malcolm?", "correct_answer": "Jurassic Park", "incorrect_answers": ["The Fly", "Independence Day", "Holy Man"]}]